Overdo it. Practice these sentences on your own, really exaggerating the word
that you think should be stressed. In the beginning, you're going to feel that this
is ridiculous. Nobody stresses this hard. Nobody talks like this. People are going
to laugh at me. Yet as much as you may stress, you're probably only going to be
stressing about half as much as you should. Practice the sentences in random
order ten times. Another reason you must over-exaggerate is because when you get
tired, emotional, or relaxed, you will stop paying attention. When this happens,
like a rubber band, you're going to snap back to the way you originally were
sounding, 10%, which is the extent to which you're exaggerating the intonation.
So, if you just stretch yourself to the exact position where you ideally want to
be, you'll go back almost completely to the old way when you relax. For practice,
then, stretch yourself far beyond the normal range of intonation, 150% or so, so
when you relax, you relax back to a standard American sound, 100%. We all do
it. Possibly about this time you're thinking, well, maybe you do this in
English, but in my language, I just really don't think we do this. I'd like you to
try a little exercise.